<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Examples</string>

    <string name="text">President Mirziyoyev puts forward new initiatives to support entrepreneurs in
        waste collection sphere
        The task has been set to increase the coverage of household waste collection in Uzbekistan
        to 95% and the volume of recycling to 40%. The President put forward new initiatives to
        support entrepreneurs in this area. 500 special vehicles will be purchased.

        Photo: Kun.uz
        On February 2, a videoconference meeting chaired by President Shavkat Mirziyoyev was held on
        the current tasks of improving the waste management system and the environmental situation,
        the implementation of the nationwide project “Green Space”.

        At the beginning of the meeting, the head of state addressed to the public.

        “We know from our childhood that our parents used to say that the yard and the environment
        should be kept clean. Our people have always considered land, water and nature sacred. It is
        said that a person who plants a tree will be rewarded. When a child is born in the family, a
        sapling is planted under his name.

        In the 21st century, when industry is highly developed around the world, environmental
        issues are on the agenda as a priority. Our generations must continue to live in a decent
        natural environment after us. To do this, we need to pay attention to nature, think not only
        of today, but also of the near and distant future.
    </string>
    <string name="start_time">Start time</string>
    <string name="location">Location</string>


    <string-array name="phones">

        <item>Redmi</item>
        <item>Poco</item>
        <item>Apple</item>
        <item>Samsung</item>
        <item>Huawei</item>

    </string-array>
    <string-array name="countries">

        <item>Uzb</item>
        <item>Rus</item>
        <item>Usa</item>
        <item>Eng</item>
        <item>Pl</item>
        <item>Uzb1</item>
        <item>Rus2</item>
        <item>Usa3</item>
        <item>En4g</item>
        <item>Pl5</item>

    </string-array>
</resources>